<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Become a Cloud Expert on Deep Dives | Cloud training with a difference.</title>
    <link>/courses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Become a Cloud Expert on Deep Dives | Cloud training with a difference.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 20:33:11 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Architecting on AWS</title>
      <link>/courses/aws/advanced-architecting/8-10-november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/aws/advanced-architecting/8-10-november-2022/</guid>
      <description>Advanced Architecting on AWS, Stockholm - Virtual Session (AAA2211SEV) About the Course This course demonstrates how to efficiently use AWS security services to stay secure in the AWS Cloud. The course focuses on the security practices that AWS recommends for enhancing the security of your data and systems in the cloud. It highlights the security features of AWS key services including compute, storage, networking, and database services. You will also learn how to leverage AWS services and tools for automation, continuous monitoring and logging, and responding to security incidents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecting on AWS</title>
      <link>/courses/aws/architecting-on-aws/november-29-december-1-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/aws/architecting-on-aws/november-29-december-1-2022/</guid>
      <description>Architecting on AWS - Virtual Session (AAR2212FIV) About the Course Architecting on AWS is for solutions architects, solution-design engineers, and developers seeking an understanding of AWS architecting. In this course, you will learn to identify services and features to build resilient, secure and highly available IT solutions on the AWS Cloud.
Architectural solutions differ depending on industry, types of applications, and business size. AWS Authorized Instructors emphasize best practices using the AWS Well-Architected Framework, and guide you through the process of designing optimal IT solutions, based on real-life scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecting with Google Compute Engine</title>
      <link>/courses/google-cloud-training/achitecting-google-compute-engine/24-26-january-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/google-cloud-training/achitecting-google-compute-engine/24-26-january-2023/</guid>
      <description>About the Course This three-day instructor-led class introduces participants to the comprehensive and flexible infrastructure and platform services provided by Google Cloud Platform, with a focus on Compute Engine. Through a combination of presentations, demos, and hands-on labs, participants explore and deploy solution elements, including infrastructure components such as networks, systems, and application services. This course also covers deploying practical solutions including securely interconnecting networks, customer-supplied encryption keys, security and access management, quotas and billing, and resource monitoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials</title>
      <link>/courses/aws/cloud-practitioner-essentials/november-14th-2022-virtual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/aws/cloud-practitioner-essentials/november-14th-2022-virtual/</guid>
      <description>About the Course On this fundamental-level full day course you will learn about AWS Cloud concepts, AWS services, security, architecture, pricing, and support to build your AWS Cloud knowledge. This course also helps you prepare for the AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner exam.
Course Price Virtual campaign price EUR 770.00 (excl VAT). Regular price EUR 890.00 (excl VAT). Language The course will be taught in English.
This course is intended for: Sales Legal Marketing Business analysts Project managers AWS Academy students Other IT-related professionals Course Outline Gain a basic understanding of the AWS Cloud and core &amp;amp; application services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Technical Essentials</title>
      <link>/courses/aws/technical-essentials/28-november-2022-virtual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/aws/technical-essentials/28-november-2022-virtual/</guid>
      <description>AWS Technical Essentials, Stockholm - Virtual Session (AES2209SEV) About the Course AWS Technical Essentials introduces you to essential AWS services and common solutions. The course covers the fundamental AWS concepts related to compute, database, storage, networking, monitoring, and security. You will start working in AWS through hands-on course experiences. The course covers the concepts necessary to increase your understanding of AWS services, so that you can make informed decisions about solutions that meet business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals</title>
      <link>/courses/microsoft-azure-training/az-900/november-16-17-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/microsoft-azure-training/az-900/november-16-17-november/</guid>
      <description>AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals, Stockholm - Virtual Session (MFU2211SEV) About the Course This two-day course will provide foundational level knowledge on cloud concepts; core Azure services; security, privacy, compliance, and trust; and Azure pricing and support.
The course will cover general cloud computing concepts, as well as general cloud computing models and services, such as Public, Private and Hybrid cloud, and Infrastructure-as-a-Service (IaaS), Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS), and Software-as-a-Service (SaaS).
It will also cover some core Azure services and solutions, as well as key Azure pillar services concerning security, privacy, compliance, and trust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing on AWS</title>
      <link>/courses/aws/developing/november-8-10-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/aws/developing/november-8-10-2022/</guid>
      <description>Developing on AWS, Helsinki - Virtual Session (ADE2211FIV) About the Course This course teaches experienced developers how to programmatically interact with AWS services to build web solutions. It guides you through a high-level architectural discussion on resource selection and dives deep into using the AWS Software Development Kits (AWS SDKs) and Command Line Interface (AWS CLI) to build and deploy your cloud applications. You will build a sample application during this course, learning how to set up permissions to the development environment, adding business logic to process data using AWS core services, configure user authentications, deploy to AWS cloud, and debug to resolve application issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FinOps Certified Practitioner</title>
      <link>/courses/finops-training/fojanuary-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/finops-training/fojanuary-2023/</guid>
      <description>FinOps certified Practitioner (FCP2301SEV) About the Course This course is an introduction to FinOps fundamentals. It’s ideal for people in a range of business, finance and technology roles, helping build your skills and credibility for driving cost savings from cloud.
This course is intended for: Cloud budget owners FinOps practitioners like FinOps Analysts, Directors of Cloud Optimisation, Cloud Operations Managers and Cloud Cost Optimisation Data Analysts Engineering roles like Principal Systems Engineers, Cloud Architects, Service Delivery Managers, Engineering Managers, Platform Engineering Directors, Senior Enterprise Architects (EA) and EA Leaders IT Programme and Portfolio Management Leaders Tech leaders like Head of Infrastructure, Head of Cloud Centre of Excellence, CTO and CIO Finance and procurement people like Technology Procurement Managers, Financial Planning Managers and Analysts, Cloud Cost Optimisation Managers and Financial Business Advisors Finance leaders like Head of IT Finance and CFO of IT Course Outline Live (virtual) 2-day, instructor-led workshop (10 hours total) Lead instructor is a real-world practising FinOps leader, supported by 1 to 2 facilitators Interactive approach, featuring group discussions and live activities using Zoom breakout rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure</title>
      <link>/courses/google-cloud-training/fundamentals-core-insfrastructure/26-september-2022-virtual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/google-cloud-training/fundamentals-core-insfrastructure/26-september-2022-virtual/</guid>
      <description>About the Course This one-day instructor-led class provides an overview of Google Cloud Platform products and services. Through a combination of presentations, demos, and hands-on labs, participants learn the value of Google Cloud Platform and how to incorporate cloud-based solutions into business strategies.
This course is intended for: Individuals planning to deploy applications and create application environments on Google Cloud Platform. Developers, systems operations professionals, and solution architects getting started with Google Cloud Platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Engineering on AWS</title>
      <link>/courses/aws/security-engineering/15-17-november-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/aws/security-engineering/15-17-november-2022/</guid>
      <description>Security Engineering on AWS - Virtual Session (ASC2211NOV) About the Course This course demonstrates how to efficiently use AWS security services to stay secure in the AWS Cloud. The course focuses on the security practices that AWS recommends for enhancing the security of your data and systems in the cloud. It highlights the security features of AWS key services including compute, storage, networking, and database services. You will also learn how to leverage AWS services and tools for automation, continuous monitoring and logging, and responding to security incidents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Operations on AWS</title>
      <link>/courses/aws/systems-operations/november-15-17-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/courses/aws/systems-operations/november-15-17-2022/</guid>
      <description>Systems Operations on AWS, Stockholm - Virtual Session (ASO2211SEV) About the Course This 3 day course teaches systems operators and anyone performing system operations functions how to install, configure, automate, monitor, secure, maintain and troubleshoot the services, networks, and systems on AWS necessary to support business applications. The course also covers specific AWS features, tools, and best practices related to these functions.
Course Price Virtual campaign price EUR 2,140.00 (excl VAT) Regular price EUR 2,490.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
